<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog | Yash Arora</title>
    <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/category/blog/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://academic-demo.netlify.app/category/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Blog</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/media/icon_hu7706b1db81251e671fce5a7b42c84e87_39138_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/category/blog/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience with amFOSS Tasks</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog post is divided in 3 sections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduction - since you took your precious time to be here. I want you to be comfortable 🤗.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tasks ✅&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience 📚&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;!-- 













&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-the-template-is-mobile-first-with-a-responsive-design-to-ensure-that-your-site-looks-stunning-on-every-device&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/master/academic.png&#34; alt=&#34;The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi 👋🏻, I&amp;rsquo;m Yash. I&amp;rsquo;m from the EAC&#39;25 Batch. I have just started to familiarize myself with the vast majority of advanced coding and I&amp;rsquo;m very eager to contribute for the welfare of society. I seek guidance in learning new languages and strengthening them. I am looking forward to participate in GSoC. Also I am intrigued by the recent boom in Deep Learning and would like to learn more about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tasks&#34;&gt;Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was quite excited upon seeing the tasks. The tasks have been designed for the people at all coding levels. From total newbies to coding maestros,there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone. amFOSS taskmakers have done quite a good job at designing these tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;experience&#34;&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This section comprises the hardships I had to face. First of all even though I said there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing for slackers. So get that to your head, you&amp;rsquo;re going nowhere if you just laze out. I&amp;rsquo;m stating this from my personal experience.
Upon seeing task-05, I thought of it as something I could complete later but after a lot of time had already passed I found it difficult to complete. After completing it, I was mentally exhausted and wasn&amp;rsquo;t to focus on any other work for the day. So hey future tryouts if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this which I know some would, treat each and every &lt;strong&gt;main&lt;/strong&gt; task equally. The most fun task to do was &lt;strong&gt;Task-02&lt;/strong&gt; as putting the co-ordinates in Google Maps was very lively. The most frustraing among all was the &lt;strong&gt;Golang Scrapper (Task-07)&lt;/strong&gt; used realising to use &lt;strong&gt;geziyor&lt;/strong&gt; after using &lt;strong&gt;colly&lt;/strong&gt; for straight 4 days was really exhausting. Now a note for future amFOSS aspirants - if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this do organise your repo from the first day itslef (it really helps on the deadline day)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
